{
	"Salt": [{
			"question": "What is the chemical formula for salt?",
			"option_1": "H2O",
			"option_2": "NaCl",
			"option_3": "CO2",
			"option_4": "C17H19NO3",
			"correct": "NaCl"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which country produces the most salt?",
			"option_1": "USA",
			"option_2": "India",
			"option_3": "China",
			"option_4": "Australia",
			"correct": "China"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the maximum recommended daily intake of salt in grams (according to WHO)?",
			"option_1": "0",
			"option_2": "2",
			"option_3": "5",
			"option_4": "10",
			"correct": "5"
		}
  ],
  "MMA": [{
    "question": "Who is the current lightweight champion in UFC?",
    "option_1": "Conor McGregor",
    "option_2": "Khabib Nurmagomedov",
    "option_3": "Alexander Gustafsson",
    "option_4": "Nate Diaz",
    "correct": "Khabib Nurmagomedov"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most common submission in UFC?",
      "option_1": "Guillotine Choke",
      "option_2": "Rear Naked Choke",
      "option_3": "Armbar",
      "option_4": "Heel Hook",
      "correct": "Rear Naked Choke"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these countries have not had a UFC champion?",
      "option_1": "Nigeria",
      "option_2": "China",
      "option_3": "India",
      "option_4": "Ireland",
      "correct": "India"
    }
  ],
  "2Pac": [{
      "question": "Besides 2Pac, he had another famous stage name. What?",
      "option_1": "Ferrari",
      "option_2": "6Pack",
      "option_3": "Frank White",
      "option_4": "Makaveli",
      "correct": "Makaveli"
    },
    {
      "question": "What year did he die?",
      "option_1": "2000",
      "option_2": "1992",
      "option_3": "1996",
      "option_4": "1991",
      "correct": "1996"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 2Pac's most played song on Spotify?",
      "option_1": "All Eyez On Me",
      "option_2": "Ghetto Gospel",
      "option_3": "Changes",
      "option_4": "Ambitionz Az A Ridah",
      "correct": "Ambitionz Az A Ridah"
    }
  ],
  "React": [{
      "question": "useEffect can be though as the combination of the following lifecycle methods except one, which?",
      "option_1": "componentWillUnmount()",
      "option_2": "componentDidMount()",
      "option_3": "componentDidUpdate()",
      "option_4": "componentWillUpdate()",
      "correct": "componentWillUnmount()"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which alternative is correct for using the useHistory Hook?",
      "option_1": "useHistory().push('/about')",
      "option_2": "useHistory().append('/about')",
      "option_3": "All of the above",
      "option_4": "None of the above",
      "correct": "useHistory().push('/about')"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you pass states declared with hooks to other components?",
      "option_1": "Yes",
      "option_2": "Yes if you wrap it in a Context",
      "option_3": "No, but it'll be possible with React 17.0",
      "option_4": "No",
      "correct": "Yes"
    }
  ]
}
